kiewit.com 2003-06-21

# Kiewit - Privacy Policy

August 6, 2002 

Peter Kiewit Sons’, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates and vendors ("Kiewit") own and operate a number of Internet domains, including but not limited to this Website (the "Website").

This statement describes Kiewit's Website privacy policies.

_**Note:**_ In this Privacy Policy, we described certain practices apply only to our on-line store (“Kiewit Company Store”). Please read these carefully if you are visiting, or intend to visit, the Kiewit Company Store. Should you have any questions about our store privacy policy, or our privacy policy in general, please send your questions to [webmaster@kiewit.com](mailto:webmaster@kiewit.com).

**Privacy Philosophy**

The Internet is rapidly changing the way we communicate and interact. While the Internet may provide access to more information and services than ever before, online activities raise new challenges, such as the privacy issues addressed in this policy. We welcome your feedback regarding this Website and our Privacy Policy. Please address all comments to [webmaster@kiewit.com](mailto:webmaster@kiewit.com).

**What Information is Collected?**

You may be asked at various times to provide data such as your name, e-mail address and phone number (the "Personally Identifiable Information"), as well as information about what you like or do not like about the Website. Kiewit collects Personally Identifiable Information online primarily to make it easier for you to use the Website, to allow us to improve our website and our services, and for us to communicate with you. Kiewit will collect additional information about you before you can purchase an item from the Kiewit Company Store. We collect and store such information as is necessary to process your purchase, fulfill your order, and improve the operation of our store.

Our data collection policies are intended to allow you to choose how much Personally Identifiable Information to provide to us. Our goal is to provide you with a satisfying online experience.

Information collected online is often defined as being either anonymous or personally identifiable:

Anonymous Information refers to information that cannot easily be tied back to a specific individual. For instance, we may know that 10,000 people visit this Privacy Policy page today, but we do not necessarily know their names, where they live, or their date of birth.

Personally Identifiable Information tells us who you are. We may need this information to provide personalized or enhanced service that you request. We also need Personally Identifiable Information and to maintain your store account once you choose to establish one and to process orders you place at the Kiewit Company Store. While we hope that you will find it beneficial to judiciously provide Personally Identifiable Information so that we can provide the best practical service to you, the amount of Personally Identifiable Information that you choose to disclose is a decision you make.

When you surf the Internet, your Internet browser automatically transmits some information to Kiewit every time you access our Website. Examples of such information include the URL of the Web page you were just on (known as the "Refer"), the IP (or Internet Protocol) address of the computer you are using, and the browser version you are using to access our site. Some of this information may be collected by Kiewit to help us improve our Website and our services. For instance, we may use this information to ensure the content you request is presented in the best format.

To activate some of the features available within the Website, we may assign "cookies" to your Internet browser. On our system, a cookie is a small text file that contains a unique identification number stored on your computer. This unique identification number automatically identifies your browser to our server computers when you interact with our Website. When you agree to provide Personally Identifiable Information directly to us, such as through registering at the Kiewit Company Store, we will assign cookies that identify you, personally, to our servers.

Following are our responses to some likely questions regarding our Privacy Policy:

**What organization is collecting the information?**

The data you provide is collected by Kiewit, or by our vendor in the case of the Kiewit Company Store. Some areas of our Website read data that creates, or has created, an Anonymous Profile. Other areas, such as the Kiewit Company Store, require you to register or login before you can purchase an item. These areas read and store Personally Identifiable Information that specifically identifies you to our servers. The Kiewit Company Store requires you to provide Personally Identifiable Information through registration before you can place an order.

**Special Note for persons under 18 years old:** The Kiewit Company Store does not sell items to anyone under the age of 18. Nor are persons under 18 years old eligible to use any Kiewit Website feature that collects Personally Identifiable Information. If you are under 18 years old and wish to purchase an item from the Kiewit Company Store or use a Website feature that requests Personally Identifiable Information, you must do so through a parent or guardian.

**How will the Anonymous Profile Information be used?**

Below is a description of some of the uses of the information that we collect and how our users benefit from these actions:

We try to pay attention to what our users use and do not use on our Website, and we modify our content appropriately. Many of the pages in our Website collect Anonymous Profile Information. The creation of an anonymous profile allows Kiewit to identify the information that users find most useful. We may use these anonymous profiles to improve our Website's content and format, and our company’s services. This is essential to our ability to provide high quality content to you.

**How will the Personally Identifiable Information be used?**

The Kiewit Company Store will collect and store Personally Identifiable Information once you register for an on-line account at the store. This includes primary contact information including a valid email address, information about your identity, shipping information, and other personal information as requested by the forms on our Website. When you purchase an item, we collect additional billing and credit card information if you have not provided that information during the registration process. We use this information to verify your identity and to bill you for your purchase.

Other areas of our Website may require that you provide Personally Identifiable Information to use a Website feature. We may use this information for internal research regarding the use of our Website and to facilitate the feature you choose to use.

To the extent possible, we indicate the informational fields that are required to purchase an item, register, or to use a feature we offer. You have the option of not providing this information to us by choosing to not purchase an item, not register, or not use the related feature of our Website.

If you correspond with us through letters or email messages, we may store such correspondence with whatever other information you have provided to us. By submitting such correspondence, you agree that we may contact you in response.

In addition to the uses described in this section, Kiewit will use the Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us and information we collect about your use of our Website to improve access to our Website, improve the content and organization of our Website, revise the items in the Kiewit Company Store, resolve disputes, and correct technical problems with the Website.

**What information will we distribute?**

Kiewit’s policy is to retain Personally Identifiable Information you submit to us, only for our use and that of our affiliated companies (including, our vendor in the case of the Kiewit Company Store). We do not sell your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties. But although we use industry standard hardware and software designed to protect your privacy, we cannot guarantee—and you should not expect—that the Personally Identifiable Information you submit to us will always remain confidential.

If you register with our Website, either at the Kiewit Company Store or elsewhere, you will be required to choose a user name and a password (when you register at the Kiewit Company Store, your user name will be your primary email address). You are responsible for protecting the confidentiality of both. Should you allow another to access our Website through your user name and password, Kiewit will assume that you are accessing our Website and you will be responsible for all actions taken in your name. By using our Website, you accept responsibility for all activity undertaken in your name.

If you register with us, you will have the option of accessing and changing your password. You may also change certain other information you provided to us. If you have any questions, send an email message to [webmaster@kiewit.com](mailto:webmaster@kiewit.com). Our server computers may retain whatever Personally Identifiable Information you have provided to us, and such data could potentially be made available for distribution to third parties as required by law, such as to law-enforcement agencies or pursuant to subpoenas or other court orders. Kiewit may also share both Anonymous Profile Information and Personally Identifiable Information to investigate allegations of fraud or other unlawful activities, civil offenses, and violations of our Terms and Conditions of Use. In such case, Kiewit shall have no obligation to notify you of, or to decline, any appropriately documented request for Personally Identifiable Information or Anonymous Profile Information.

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Kiewit Websites. Kiewit does not control the information collection and distribution policies on Internet domains other than on Kiewit Internet domains. As a service to our users, the Kiewit Website may provide links to other sites. Kiewit is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage all users to read the privacy statements of each and every Website.

**What choices are available regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information?**

We encourage you to share information only with those websites that provide true value to you in exchange for your information and that commit to privacy practices that are acceptable to you. We believe that Kiewit's websites provide such value, but it is ultimately your choice to share Personally Identifiable Information with Kiewit.

While Kiewit does not sell any Personally Identifiable Information you submit to our Website to any other parties, Kiewit reserves the right to use such information for any lawful purpose, including but not limited to recruiting, marketing, performance monitoring and statistical analysis.

Kiewit reserves the right to update this policy. When we do, we will send an announcement by email to the primary email address of each registered user or by placing a notice on our Website.

Kiewit also reserves the right to send registration confirmations, Service Alerts and similar messages to our users to inform them of specific changes that may impact their ability to use our Website, regardless of such users' e-mail contact opt-in status. Kiewit retains these rights because we may need the right to contact you as a matter of law or regarding matters that may be important to you.

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be submitted via e-mail to webmaster@kiewit.com If we have not responded to your inquiry in a timely manner or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact us at 402-342-2052, extension 2685. Our mailing address is: ______________ Kiewit Plaza, Omaha, Nebraska 68131.
